biggeekdaddy.com 2018-05-01

# Privacy Policy

What information do I collect?

I collect information from you when you subscribe to my newsletter. When subscribing to my newsletter you will be   
asked to enter your e-mail address.

You may, however, visit this site anonymously.

I use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit BigGeekDaddy.com These companies may use   
information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other   
Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more   
information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, 

[click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Additionally:  
* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other   
sites on the Internet.

* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the

[ Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

* Google, also uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads on my site. You can find a complete list of

[Global Certified 3rd Party Vendors for Google](http://support.google.com/dfp_sb/bin/answer.py?hl=en-GB&answer=94149&topic=16148&ctx=topic) so you can visit these websites to opt out of cookies (if the vendor or ad   
network offers this capability). Users can also opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the   
[Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

What do I use your information for?

Any of the information I collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To send periodic emails:  
The email address you provide may be used to send you my Video of the Day email in addition to receiving occasional   
site news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, I include detailed unsubscribe   
instructions at the bottom of each email.

Do I use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web   
browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and   
remember certain information

I use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that   
I can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. I may contract with third-party service providers to assist me   
in better understanding my site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on   
our behalf except to help me conduct and improve my business.

Do I disclose any information to outside parties?

I do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not   
include trusted third parties who assist me in operating my website, conducting my business, or servicing you, so long   
as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. I may also release your information when I believe release   
is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce my site policies, or protect my or others rights, property, or safety.   
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or   
other uses.

Third party links

Occasionally, at my discretion, I may include or offer third party products or services on my website. These third party   
sites have separate and independent privacy policies. I therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and   
activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, I seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about   
these sites.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because I value your privacy I have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online   
Privacy Protection Act. I therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

I am in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), I do not knowingly   
collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. This website, products and services are all directed to   
people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through my website and not to information collected   
offline.

Your Consent

By using my site, you consent to my online privacy policy.

Changes to my Privacy Policy

If I decide to change my privacy policy, I will post those changes on this page.

Contact me at bgd at biggeekdaddy.com
